Boyhood
EP02
Dear teachers and students
Welcome to mgtv's
brand-new customized show for VIPs, Boyhood.
This is the scene of the finals of Boy School Singer Competition.
Welcome.
After fierce contesting,
the "top three" of the contest finally emerged.
First,
let's welcome lovely and charming Little Sun of the new generation,
Proud Boy, Pax Congo.
Hello, everyone. I'm one
of the top three.
You can call me Gangdan.
Hello.
Come on.
One of the top three has already appeared.
Next, let's welcome Kido,
a hot-blooded boy
who was born for the stage
to sing and compose music.
Hello.
I'm Kido, born for the stage.
Born for the stage.
Finally, let's welcome an affectionate boy who loves music
and tells stories with songs.
Edmond Leung
Hello.
He comes out with a little guilty.
It falls off.
This year's finals still follow
the traditional boosting competition rule of Boy School.
The five teenagers beside me
are Boy Group of the competition.
They will help you.
Let's welcome Boy Group.
We are Boy Group for guarding you.
Please guard them well.
Please say it.
Brave Pax Congo
is not afraid of difficulties.
Sing for love, Edmond Leung.
We are all spoony people.
Hooray.
Do I have one?
I'll always be with you.
I'll guard the whole universe for you.
Do you think
the feeling of being professed by a boy
is actually quite subtle?
Well.
Let's get right into the first round.
The TV will show photos of singers in turn.
Please sing his/her songs
by identifying the singer in the photo.
If you're right, you can score.
If you're wrong, or you don't answer within five seconds,
you can't score
and you need to be punished.
Please answer in turn.
There are three musical eras here.
Before the start of each round,
you can choose
whether you need the help of teenagers or not.
If the answer is yes,
the teenager will sit beside you to help.
If he is right, you can also score.
If you ask him to help you in this round,
you can't do it again in the next round.
Let's start in turn.
First,
numerous outstanding singers appeared
in Cassette Era from the 1980s to the mid-1990s
in Chinese music.
Let me ask you first.
Do you remember whose cassette
you bought for the first time?
The first cassette.
I remember when I was in primary school,
I bought Samuel Hui's The Private Eyes.
I remember the first one I bought was Nicholas Tse's.
Because Nicholas Tse
was very cool and handsome at that time,
and had long hair.
When he wrote that song,
I was actually in his studio.
His studio in Hong Kong.
Really?
Yes.
Very predestined.
It's a little magical.
I forgot the first one I bought.
But I remember the first one
I heard when I was a child
was Yungdrung Gyal's The Miracle.
It seems that...
Many people should not have heard of it.
I can't believe you can sing.
Please tell your stories.
The first song I bought was
Two butterflies.
I remember it very well.
So your personal music career
is also closely related to butterflies.
I really don't know. It's a coincidence.
I've never bought a cassette about music.
Since I was a child, I have been exposed to
cassettes for teaching English.
His cassettes are all about teaching.
There is a generation gap between us and him.
Now let's start the first round at once.
Cassette Era.
First of all, Edmond Leung, please get ready.
The singer's name is?
Jeff Chang
You're right.
Okay, Pax Congo, please listen to the question.
This's so easy.
He doesn't know.
Sing the chorus.
He forgot again.
Please give Kido extra points.
I feel like you were a repeater.
Kido
Please listen to the question.
She has a lot of songs.
Is it so sudden?
You're unprepared and it's unpredictable.
I've just been affected.
Because when I was just about to sing,
Pax Congo spoke to me.
He did it on purpose.
Please give me one more chance, okay?
OK.
That's the song I just sang to you.
She has a lot of songs.
I can't believe you just accused me.
I'm wrong.
You can't score.
Next, Edmond Leung, please look at the question.
You're right.
Pax Congo, please listen to the question.
I really don't know.
Please punish me.
You must know her.
It's just that you may not have seen
her old photos.
Who is she?
This is Mao Amin.
Mao Amin?
Yes.
She is so beautiful.
She is too fashionable.
What age is this from?
This is a coat from the 1980s.
She's a pioneer.
Edmond Leung, please listen to the question.
I know this.
My idol.
I'll think of one first.
Representative.
Right.
He can't remember until he is punished.
Pax Congo, please look at the question.
Walk Past That Coffee Shop.
No?
Wait a minute, Pax Congo.
This can't work?
This is not BiBi Zhou?
This is Rose Zhang.
Many of her songs are familiar to me.
She is the Queen of Disco.
I'm right to be punished.
The last question.
Come on.
Please look at the question.
This's so easy.
Jonathan Lee.
He's done.
Punish him.
He can't remember.
I acted in a TV show called Upon The Mountain.
I'm stuck.
It's normal. Tapes also tend to get stuck.
You're right.
The one just now is considered a canvass for yourself.
We just saw a lot of
singers from Cassette Era
that you are very familiar with.
For example, Teresa Teng
was the Goddess
of many people in that era.
Let me ask you.
Who was your goddess
when you were young?
I like to hear this.
Goddess.
I remember.
Who?
I liked Jam Hsiao very much at that time.
He just finished a show.
Later, Amber Kuo
and Jam Hsiao made an advertisement together.
That music is...
She is cute and beautiful.
Mainly thank Jam Hsiao
for letting me know Amber Kuo.
If you let me say my goddess,
I was a little unhappy just now,
because I didn't answer the question about her correctly just now.
She is Sandy Lam.
Sandy Lam.
I remember I liked her very much
when I was a student.
I sometimes listened to her songs in class at that time.
Then when I made my second album,
I invited her agent Xu Yuan
to help me.
She invited Sandy Lam
to help me sing.
I couldn't believe it at that time.
She is really
the most important goddess in my mind.
Please add the point
about Sandy Lam
from Edmond Leung just now.
Please.
Okay,
let's move on to
the second round, CD Era.
Before we start this round,
let me ask you.
Which was the first CD you bought?
I...
Let me tell you about a rather special experience.
I found my first CD in third grade.
It was found
when my friends and I
hung out in summer.
That's a CD of Michael Jackson.
You're amazing.
But we didn't know who he was.
They didn't like it when they got it.
So they gave it to me. After I listened to it,
I put my school uniform...
Then from then on,
I entered another field of music.
Pax Congo, I think your life
is on the wrong side.
Why?
Because the reason God
let you to find a CD of Michael Jackson
is to make you
a very good singer who can both sing and dance.
You get the idea.
But you become a rock singer.
Your life is completely on the wrong side.
No.
I think this experience is quite amazing.
Right.
Me too.
The first CD I bought
was Michael Jackson's
Bad.
Well.
Next, in CD Era,
you can choose
whether to ask them for help or not.
I think the problems in this round should not be difficult.
I think the problems in Digital Era are the most difficult.
I don't need help.
Me too.
OK,
let's go straight to CD Era.
Let's start with Edmond Leung.
Please look at the question.
You're right.
Pax Congo, please look at the question.
She has a lot of songs.
You're right.
Kido, please look at the question.
Are you touched?
Yes.
The next question is very strange. Please look at the question.
This handsome guy looks familiar.
Sing a song at will.
You can sing at will.
This song is very nice. Cantonese is really nice.
Well.
Pax Congo, please look at the question.
She's so beautiful.
I sang it today.
Which song do you wanna sing?
Searching For You.
How to sing it?
Freezed immediately.
Freezed where I were.
Both of CDs and tapes can make you jammed.
Yes.
Kido, please look at the photo.
You can sing without hesitation.
Great!
The final round.
Edmond Leung, please look at the photo.
Original Gangster.
I don't know her.
Han Hong
She was too young at that time.
You're really good at looking for photos.
Especially the photos at that time.
Pax Congo, please look at the photo.
The echo effect in our room
is good.
I wondered why
we didn't take part in the singer competition.
It turns out that we're unqualified.
Applaud and cheer them.
Kido, please look at the last photo.
AMEI
I at once know.
OK. You're right.
OK.
We're also familiar with CD Era.
There were some singers like
perfect partners in that era.
For example, Hong Kong Four Heavenly Kings.
Are you familiar with them?
Andy Lau
Aaron Kwok
And?
Leon Lai Ming
Jacky Cheung
Yes.
It took
them a long time to figure it out.
OK.
After CD Era
we're coming to Digital music Era
that you're worried about.
Yes.
Let me ask you three first.
Yes, I will.
You should choose
who you want to use respectively.
Then I'll choose Li Wenjie.
Of course, Hou Zhuocheng.
I think Shao Mingming
pays more attention to the Internet.
I choose Shao Mingming.
You two should learn from me.
I'm coming here now.
Give me a seat.
Next
there are songs that you can download
through mp3.
Start with Edmond Leung.
Jason Zhang. The World.
It's LOVE.
Hou Zhuocheng is like a consultant.
He reported all the information.
For Edmond Leung, he may
feel distanced from Jason Zhang.
Jason Zhang
A little bit.
But for Hou Zhuocheng
he's very familiar with him.
Yes. Yes.
You can sing on his behalf.
It's LOVE.
OK. One point for Hou Zhuocheng.
It's right if Boy Group can sing it out.
Hou Zhuocheng, keep going.
Come on.
Keep going. Keep going.
Next, Pax Congo.
There's no need to see. It's himself.
Really?
I wonder who he is.
He can remember the lyrics so clearly.
This photo is too old.
It was a photo seven years ago.
Our director team
had never looked for the latest photos.
Come on, Kido. Please look at the photo.
Why?
Who prepared this photo?
Who is it?
Why?
Kido, you looked fashionable at that time.
You were the most fashionable
Internet hunk at that time.
I should sing first, right?
Excellent!
OK. Next one.
Next one.
Come on.
Charlie
This is Na Ying's song.
Yes. It's Silence.
Penalize one point.
Penalize.
What I wanted to say is
please charge Hou Zhuocheng.
His voice is getting lower and lower.
He wanted to sing Bigfish.
Think about it.
One more chance for you.
You can't even sing Bigfish.
Shi Kai, come on.
Louder.
You left the vocal cords at home?
Please charge him. His voice is low, too.
He's afraid that we might hear him.
Next, Pax Congo. Please look at the photo.
Hua Chenyu
Excellent!
OK. It's our turn.
Silence
Silence. Right.
Sing!
The songs of Silence? Let me think about it.
How to sing Silence?
Is it his song?
Yes.
It's his Little Star.
Sit here, please.
I dare not take your place.
I'm a little nervous.
I recognized him, but I didn't remember his song.
The part of Digital music Era is over.
Everyone did well just now.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Is there any chance?
There are plenty of chances later.
My desire for victory is coming up again.
Yes, me too.
Defeat them.
OK. The last round
tested the brothers' reserves in the music circles.
The second challenge is called
Listen Carefully.
First, fill in the blanks
according to the songs you hear.
And every brother
has a chance to use a tip.
You can make any boy
in Boy Group help you to listen.
OK, no problem. Come on.
Please listen to the question.
What's this?
What song is this?
Everyone, please show your board.
It must be eight.
Eight.
Eight "showbizs", nine "inno-s" and one "-cent".
There is no "innocent", isn't there?
Isn't it "spring"?
It's "pure".
It isn't "innocent".
You can't change it now.
OK. I'm sure that
I can see no correct answer now.
OK. One more time.
OK. I'm done.
Take it easy.
Wait for Edmond Leung.
We can write a multiplication sign and a number.
13 "showbizs".
And
spring festival, spring festival, spring festival.
Edmond Leung
It's "pure".
All of us can see you're changing the answer.
You don't have to change it.
It doesn't matter.
OK. Edmond Leung's answer is
13 "showbizs" and five "spring festivals".
12 "showbizs" and five "pures".
12 "showbizs" and five "pures". Congratulations!
It's called Into Chinese Showbiz.
It's the theme song of a movie.
You're right.
The movie got the lowest score
in the history of Douban.
My friend played in it.
He must have few friends.
Everyone. The next question.
It's the theme song
of a boy in Boy Group present.
Really?
Come on, everyone. Please listen to the question.
It's my song.
A Drunk Butterfly.
Please listen to the question.
I'm absolutely right.
Touch on lightly.
A knot that can no longer be untied.
You're right.
Come on. The original singer Shao Mingming.
Please show yourself.
Well, really!
OK. The next question.
You can become light if you're right.
Light?
Don't talk nonsense. Come on.
Please listen to the question.
I know it.
Ultraman.
Brothers, I've shouted out
the correct answer by
the standard of a host.
Edmond Leung, you can use mine.
What? OK.
I'm coming.
It doesn't matter if I miswrite, right?
It matters.
I wrote Pinyin.
Please show your board.
You're right.
He used some singing skills.
Although he used some skills while singing
his words...
Wait a minute.
Don't show me the correct answer.
I was just hesitating.
It should be like this, right?
OK. You're right.
Come on. Kido.
I wrote Pinyin.
You can't even write pinyin correctly.
You have to do like this?
It makes me look so illiterate.
Mine is brilliant.
No, you're missing something.
Yes. Pax Congo.
Congratulations! You're right.
The next question.
Please listen to the question, brothers.
Write it down, everyone. What are you waiting for?
Copy mine. He didn't say you couldn't copy others'.
Shao Mingming, you've found my bug.
Excellent.
You're really clever.
The classmate is so good.
Kido
What are you doing?
What happened?
Are you painting?
I can only remember "a kiss".
A kiss is enough.
Shao Mingming, you can sing with Edmond Leung.
Don't scold me.
The song is well arranged.
♪ You gave me a light kiss ♪
♪ I felt crazy ♪
♪ The atmosphere began to heat up ♪
♪ Dangerous and charming ♪
The melody is easy to remember.
♪ You gave me a light kiss ♪
That's all.
Shandong dialect is coming out.
Congratulations! Edmond Leung and Pax Congo.
You're right in this round.
Please listen to the question.
Ready. The question is coming.
I cannot understand.
I just understand...
Edmond Leung can only hear "Congratulations".
I only heard "Congratulations", too.
Yes. It's not just Cantonese.
The point is that it's not a word.
How do we guess?
We can listen to it once more.
Come on. Please listen to the question.
I don't want to listen to it.
It's difficult.
I wonder if anyone at the scene
can write one correctly
except "Congratulations".
You're right on the right track.
Let's see the correct answer.
Too difficult.
It's so difficult.
What's "CDX"?
♪ Here's a past ♪
♪ CDX ♪
Do you know what that means?
I have no idea.
Being in love.
You are right.
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
It's the first letter of "being in love" in Pinyin.
Now, the five of you
come up with an acronym for your brothers to guess.
If any brother can get the correct answer first,
he will be given one point.
It must be something simple.
Show something a little harder.
Harder?
Simple questions are a little boring.
Choose some popular but difficult ones.
Then you can choose one.
TQL
It's so hard.
This one is really hard.
I feel we seldom use it.
TQL
Brothers are TQL.
I know it.
TQL means too awesome.
Too awesome.
Because Hou Zhuocheng says that
brothers are TQL.
Brothers are TQL.
It's amazing.
So it means too awesome.
Let's do another one.
Kido has the...
He's got...
Handsome?
Something like that.
Beautiful?
Ma what?
Ma Dongmei
Ma Dong what?
What Dongmei?
Ma Dongmei
Ma what?
Ma
Stop playing this game.
Okay.
Let's show it.
The correct answer is...
All three of you
look fantastic.
It's too hard.
Let's come to the next question.
This is a song
that everyone is dancing on the short video platform recently.
Here's the question.
If you tell me whose song it is, I will know it.
It's a song of G.E.M.
The last sentence is "born invincible".
It's like glass.
No.
Use tips if you have.
Look, they don't get the answer.
I think I'm all right.
I also think I'm all right.
How about Edmond Leung?
I think I'm all wrong.
That's what I hear.
The last one is incompetent and powerless.
OK, I'll announce the right answer.
Let's take a look at the right answer.
No one can match.
Born invincible.
They were both wrong at this sentence.
Then I'm all right.
I'm all right, too.
We're all wrong.
Use tips if you have.
Look, they don't get the answer.
Come on.
If you tell me whose song it is, I will know it.
I think I'm all right.
I also think I'm all right.
We're all wrong.
Okay, so we're done with this round.
Next, there will be the third round of performances.
Next, our brothers will cooperate with
Boy Group
to perform a song.
Everyone sings part of it.
Then the karaoke system
scores the group singing.
In the end, the group with the highest score wins.
Sign up actively.
I put the initiative in your hands.
Sun Yuwei
Because he sang something about me
when they introduced themselves.
Do you agree?
He hesitated.
You hesitated.
Shao Mingming
Believe me.
What track would you like to choose?
《Check-in》
Come on, self-match.
I choose Pax Congo.
OK.
I can sing, but it may be out of tune.
It doesn't matter.
What track do you want to choose?
Ear Blindness.
All right.
OK.
Hou Zhuocheng and Edmond Leung, what track do you want to choose?
Love Once in a Lifetime.
OK.
Then let's start
the stage show of Sing Well.
First of all, let's welcome the first group
Pax Congo and his partner.
He ranked first on the court.
Please.
Come on!
Hello, everyone. I'm Pax Congo.
That's all. So simple?
Yes, that's all.
My self introduction is a little special.
Follow the beat.
But I will never hate intelligence.
Since I'm from the island.
Just be a child who is always steaming hot.
AKA Little Zebra, Li Wenjie.
Your nickname is special.
I'm known for rap.
Become...
What?
How can a rapper become a monk?
I also prepared a little surprise
in this song.
OK.
Come on.
OK, please start.
Is this the little surprise he prepared?
It's too high.
You blame the song instead of yourself.
With my help,
your number one position may not be so stable.
It doesn't matter.
Congratulations.
You get 3094 points.
Cool.
If I sing alone, I should score higher.
I'm kidding.
It is possible that
they sing such a song deliberately.
Do you have any hidden tasks?
You have a hidden task, right?
No.
He's disloyal.
Yes!
His self-introduction at the beginning...
He never remembers...
And he sings on the backing track randomly.
Yes.
He did it on purpose.
The melody's a little off.
OK, then let's welcome the second group.
Hello, everyone. I'm Edmond Leung.
Hello, everyone.
I am Hou Zhuocheng,
the best football player in Boy Group.
What is the song you are going to sing?
Love Once in a Lifetime.
This is my song in 1995.
This song is groovy.
Good.
Hou Zhuocheng, you're cool.
The final score is
4957 points.
Okay, next, our third group.
Are you ready?
OK.
Hi, I'm Kido.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Sun Yuwei.
I'm sorry, bro.
I'm a musical "idiot".
Get out of here.
I'm kidding you.
No problem.
Enjoy it.
And then can I have two chairs?
You want to dance.
Create the atmosphere.
I feel a little better sitting down.
It's more like a karaoke bar.
Okay, let's start.
Come on.
Take it easy.
It doesn't matter.
I really try hard.
Brother,
help me.
Wait, I find one point.
I've been looking at that score.
When Li Wenjie is singing,
that score is about ten points.
Although Sun Yuwei is saying,
he has 69 points.
The final score is
4833 points.
That's good.
I'm happy.
Come on, please come to me
and stand in a row.
Now the performances of our three groups
are all over.
First, let's give them applause.
Now we are about to announce
the final result.
Combined with the total score,
there are two champions
who have the highest score
in the Boy School Singer Competition.
Let's congratulate Pax Congo
and Edmond Leung.
Wait a minute.
I think this rule
actually make me shameless.
There are only three people in total.
If you rank first, second, third and fourth,
I'll take the third place and admit it.
Two people win the championship,
so what am I?
Oh, my God.
You are the runner-up who win the second place!
Congratulations to the runner-up!
Then next, let's ask Shao Mingming
to present us the champion gift box.
Thank you.
Let's open it together.
One, two, three, four.
The gift box
is summer limited refreshing package.
Is it all right?
Watermelon...
This is used to comfort you with fantasy.
What is this?
Is it an electric fan?
Yes.
We put on make-up
and then use it.
We won't sweat easily.
Okay.
The "sound" of spring breeze is for you.
With the award ceremony over,
our finals also come to an end.
Although the happy time is short,
the excitement of Boy School
can always be expected.
We thank all the contestants for their participation.
Thanks.
See you later.
I'll do a magic trick.
My boyhood
is a dream time for me.
Because that's when
I became a singer
from a football player.
My boyhood
is when I think of my family and friends at that time,
I will feel happy.
Let's welcome our classmates
to
the No Street.
The challenge begins.
Introduce the four of us
with four different voices.
Twenty winks.
Is it okay?
Please perform.
Mystical smile.
This is good.
Whether this challenge has been completed or not,
let's make a question mark first.
The auction challenge of the second course
is to hit the forehead.
Five times.
Six times.
Nine times.
Twenty times.
Stop.
You're crazy.
I'm regretful.
Brother
Don't you feel dizzy?
He disturbs others.
Too much.